export default [{
	"id": "holy-moly",
	"question": "Why did the baker stop selling doughnuts?",
	"answer": "Got tired of the hole thing.",
},
{
	"id": "no-sql",
	"question": "A couple of relational database admins walked into a NoSQL bar. A little while later they walked out.",
	"answer": "Because they couldn't find a table!",
},
{
	"id": "kind-star",
	"question": "What kind of star could hurt you?",
	"answer": "A shooting star.",
},
{
	"id": "spider-shop",
	"question": "Where do spiders shop?",
	"answer": "The Web.",
},
{
	"id": "cache-rest",
	"question": "What did the website do when it felt sluggish?",
	"answer": "It cached up on some REST.",
},
{
	"id": "await-coffee",
	"question": "What’s a JavaScript developer's favorite type of coffee?",
	"answer": "Async! ☕️",
},
{
	"id": "symbol-spins",
	"question": "Why is the loading symbol so good at keeping secrets?",
	"answer": "Because it always spins the truth!",
},
{
	"id": "carry-on",
	"question": "Why did the webpage break up with the loading bar?",
	"answer": "Because they couldn’t move forward, they were always stuck in the middle!",
},
{
	"id": "classic-array",
	"question": "Why did the JavaScript array go out of bounds?",
	"answer": "Because it didn't know its own length.",
},
{
	"id": "two-equality",
	"question": "What is the difference between == and === comparison operators?",
	"answer": "JavaScript: Well, with == I kind of guess, but with === I'm really sure.",
}]